

ABOUT ME

I have been working as a frontend developer for over 4 years, using JavaScript to create web Uls. I am excited to experiment with new UI designs and learn new technologies. Building UIs with different technologies is challenging, but it helps me enhance my skills.

CONTACT





Fajrin Mahyuddin

SKILLS

ReactNative PHP] ReactJS CSS] Laravel Jquery Rest API

Styled Component ExpressJS

Scss / Sass / Less **Typescript**

Firebase ` Javascript) NextJS Svelte Git

Supabse) InertiaJS GraphQL

FAJRIN MAHYUDDIN

Front End Developer



JOB EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer, Jan 2016 - Aug 2016 at PT Cipta Sejati Revolution (Makassar - Indonesia)

Freelance, Jan 2019 - Nov 2019 as freelance web developer (Makassar - Indonesia)

Frontend Developer. Nov 2019 - Oct 2021 at Pallaka Studio (Makassar - Indonesia)

Frontend Developer, Oct 2021 - Present at Zodiac Solution Pte Ltd (Singapore)

EDUCATION

Senior High School at Majene, 2009 - 2012

Diploma III of Electrical Engineering at State Polytechnic of Ujung Pandang, 2012 - 2015

Bachelor Degree of Electrical Engineering at Tadulako University, 2017 - 2019

PREVIEW PROJECT

Coffee-App E-Commerce dan portal artikel https://coffee-app-ssr.vercel.app

EGS AMS - Aplikasi Menejemen Surat https://amspro.pallakastudio.com

Landing Page - Landing page with LaslesVPN https://landing-page-fajrin.netlify.app

Sitinaja - Sistem Informasi Jaksrada https://sitinaja.pallakastudio.com

Admin PPDB Online - Admin Page Penerimaan Perserta Didik Baru https://adpas.ayoppdb.id

FIND ME

Official Site - https://fajrin-mahyuddin.github.io

Github - https://github.com/Fajrin-Mahyuddin

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/fajrin-mahyuddin-a65111131

Twitter - @Fajrin_M

HOBBIES





